Guide to the Portland Reporter Photographs Collection 1960-1964
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- Subject Files, circa 1900-1965; 1960-1965; Series A
  - Islands--Galapagos--Moody, 1961 (Box-folder 23/18)
  - Islands--Shaw, 1962 (Box-folder 23/19)
  - Jacksonville, Or., 1964 (Box-folder 23/20)
  - Jade, 1962 (Box-folder 23/21)
  - Jail--Portland, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 23/22)
  - Jantzen Beach, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 23/23)
  - Jantzen, Inc., 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 23/24)
  - Japanese in Portland, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 23/25)
  - Japanese in the United States, 1964 (Box-folder 23/26)
  - Japanese Garden Society, 1964 (Box-folder 23/27)
  - Jewels, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 23/28)
  - Jewish Community Center, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 23/29)
  - John Deere Co., 1961 (Box-folder 23/30)
  - Johnson Creeek--Flood, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 23/31)
  - Journal Building, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 23/32)
  - Judo, 1962 (Box-folder 23/33)
  - Junior Miss, 1963 (Box-folder 23/34)
  - Junior Museum, 1961 (Box-folder 23/35)
  - Jury, 1962 (Box-folder 23/36)
  - Juvenile delinquency, 1962 (Box-folder 23/37)
  - Kahneeta Hot Springs, 1964 (Box-folder 23/38)
  - Kahneeta Hot Springs, 1961 (Box-folder 128/10)
  - Kaiser Cement and Gympsum Corp., 1964 (Box-folder 23/39)
  - Kalama, Wash., 1962 (Box-folder 23/40)
  - Kenyans in Portland, 1963 (Box-folder 23/41)
  - Key West, Fla., 1962 (Box-folder 23/42)
  - King Building Supply, 1962 (Box-folder 23/43)
  - King City, 1964 (Box-folder 23/44)
  - Kitchen, 1963 (Box-folder 23/45)
  - Klamath County Jail, 1961 (Box-folder 23/46)
  - Knott Street Community Center, 1961 (Box-folder 23/47)
  - Korean orphans, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 23/48)
  - Ku Klux Klan, 1964 (Box-folder 23/49)
  - Kupp Motor Co., 1961 (Box-folder 23/50)
  - Labor, 1960 (Box-folder 24/1)
  - Labor--International Woodworkers of America, 1963 (Box-folder 24/2)
  - Labor--Longshoremen, 1964 (Box-folder 24/3)
  - Labor--Paper workers, 1964 (Box-folder 24/4)
  - Labor--Portland Youth Work Project, 1964 (Box-folder 24/5)
  - Labor relations--Strikes, 1964 (Box-folder 24/6)
  - Ladder, 1964 (Box-folder 24/7)
  - La Maison Hoire, 1960 (Box-folder 24/8)
  - Lake, undated (Box-folder Oversize B1/11)
  - Lake--Billy Chinook, 1964 (Box-folder 24/9)
  - Lake--Crystal Springs, 1964 (Box-folder 24/10)
  - Lake Louise, 1961 (Box-folder 24/11)
  - Lake Oswego, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 24/12)
  - Lake Oswego Hunt Club, 1962 (Box-folder 24/13)
  - Lake Valley, Or., 1962 (Box-folder 24/14)
  - Lambert Gardens, 1962 (Box-folder 24/15)
  - Lamps, 1964 (Box-folder 24/16)
  - Land--Private, 1963 (Box-folder 24/17)
  - Landslides, 1962 (Box-folder 24/18)
  - Lane Valley Youth Camp, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 24/19)
  - Lanterns, 1960; 1964 (Box-folder 24/20)
  - Laurelhurst Club, 1962 (Box-folder 24/21)
  - Law Day, 1962 (Box-folder 24/22)
  - Leaves, 1960 (Box-folder 24/23)
  - Legionnaires in action, 1964 (Box-folder 24/24)
  - Legislature--Oregon, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 24/25)
  - Lewis and Clark College, 1960-1961; 1964 (Box-folder 24/26)
  - Lewis and Clark Trail, 1964 (Box-folder 24/27)
  - Lexington, Or., 1961 (Box-folder 24/28)
  - Liberty Bell, 1963 (Box-folder 24/29)
  - Library--Portland, 1964 (Box-folder 24/30)
  - Libraries--Rockwood Branch, 1962 (Box-folder 24/31)
  - Lie detectors, 1962 (Box-folder 24/32)
  - Lifeguards, 1964 (Box-folder 24/33)
  - Lightning, 1961 (Box-folder 24/34)
  - Light house--Coquille River, 1964 (Box-folder 24/35)
  - Lincoln County--Central Lincoln PUD Branch Office, 1961 (Box-folder 24/36)
  - Linfield College, 1962 (Box-folder 24/37)
  - Linnton, 1963 (Box-folder 24/38)
  - Linnton Community Center, 1964 (Box-folder 24/39)
  - Lions Club, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 24/40)
  - Lipman's, 1960 (Box-folder 24/41)
  - Lipman's Eastport, 1960 (Box-folder 24/42)
  - Literature--Obscene, 1964 (Box-folder 24/43)
  - Lizards, 1960 (Box-folder 24/44)
  - Lloyd Center, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 24/45-47)
  - Lloyd Plaza, 1964 (Box-folder 24/48)
  - Lloyds of London, 1964 (Box-folder 24/49)
  - Lobsters, 1961 (Box-folder 25/1)
  - Logs, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 25/2)
  - Lolo Pass, 1963 (Box-folder 25/3)
  - Long Beach, Wash., 1962 (Box-folder 25/4)
  - Longshoremen--Portland, 1960-1961; 1964 (Box-folder 25/5)
  - Loom, 1964 (Box-folder 25/6)
  - Los Angeles, Calif, 1961 (Box-folder 25/7)
  - Lost Lake, 1961 (Box-folder 25/8)
  - Lucia Bride, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 25/9-10)
  - Machines--Straddle carriers, 1962 (Box-folder 25/11)
  - MacLaren School, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 25/12)
  - Marriage, 1964 (Box-folder 25/13)
  - Military--Pageant of flags, undated (Box-folder 25/14)
  - Miss Oregon Pageant, 1964, June 25-27 (Box-folder 25/15)
  - Monuments, 1964 (Box-folder 25/16)
  - Murder site, Troy, Mich., 1964 (Box-folder 25/17)
  - Musicians, undated (Box-folder 25/18)
  - Nails, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 25/19)
  - NASA--Technical Services, undated (Box-folder 25/20)
  - National Guard--Oregon, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 25/21)
  - National League--Cincinnati Reds, 1964 (Box-folder 25/22)
  - Necanicum River, 1961 (Box-folder 25/23)
  - Negroes, 19661-1963 (Box-folder 25/24)
  - Negroes--Alabama, 1963 (Box-folder 25/25)
  - Negroes--Maryland, 1963 (Box-folder 25/26)
  - Negroes--New York, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 25/27)
  - Negroes--Ohio, 1963 (Box-folder 25/28)
  - Nehalem Bay, 1962 (Box-folder 25/29)
  - Neighborhood House, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 25/30)
  - Nelson Equipment Co., 1962 (Box-folder 25/31)
  - New England--Old Sturbridge Village, 1964 (Box-folder 25/32)
  - New System Laundry--Fire, 1960 (Box-folder 25/33)
  - New York, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 25/34)
  - New York--Harbor, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 25/35)
  - New York World's Fair, 1963 (Box-folder 25/36)
  - Newburg, Or., 1962 (Box-folder 25/37)
  - Newport, Or., 1961 (Box-folder 25/38)
  - Nightclubs, 1964 (Box-folder 25/39)
  - Norge Laundry and Cleaning Village, 1961 (Box-folder 25/40)
  - Northern Rhodesia, 1964 (Box-folder 25/41)
  - Northwest Auto Wreckers Assoc., 1961 (Box-folder 26/1)
  - Northwest Natural Gas, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 26/2)
  - Nuclear explosions, 1962 (Box-folder 26/3)
  - Nudist camp, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 26/4)
  - Nuns, 1964 (Box-folder 26/5)
  - Nursery--Providence, 1963 (Box-folder 26/6)
  - Nuts, 1961 (Box-folder 26/7)
  - Nyssa, Or., 1960 (Box-folder 26/8)
  - Oakland, Or., 1962 (Box-folder 26/9)
  - Oaks Amusement Park, 1964 (Box-folder 26/10)
  - Oceanlake, Or., 1960-1961 (Box-folder 26/11)
  - Office buildings, 1960 (Box-folder 26/12)
  - Oil drilling rig, 1964 (Box-folder 26/13)
  - Olds and King (1871 photo), 1966 (Box-folder 26/14)
  - Olympic games, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 26/15)
  - Olympic Pipeline Co., 1964 (Box-folder 26/16)
  - Omark Industries, 1963 (Box-folder 26/17)
  - Oneonta Gorge, 1961 (Box-folder 26/18)
  - Opera-- Fidelio, 1963 (Box-folder 26/19)
  - Opera--New Savoy, 1962 (Box-folder 26/20)
  - Oranges, undated (Box-folder 26/21)
  - Oregon (Welcome sign on highway), undated (Box-folder 26/22)
  - Oregon--Central, 1961 (Box-folder 26/23)
  - Oregon Ceramic Studios, 1962 (Box-folder 26/24)
  - Oregon City, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 26/25)
  - Oregon Coast, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 26/26)
  - Oregon College of Education, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 26/27)
  - Oregon Dairy Princess, 1964 (Box-folder 26/28)
  - Oregon Gun Hawks, 1963 (Box-folder 26/29)
  - Oregon Humane Society, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 26/30)
  - Oregon Hunting and Retriever Club, 1962 (Box-folder 26/31)
  - Oregon Historical Society, 1964 (Box-folder 26/32)
  - Oregon Junior Miss, 1964 (Box-folder 26/33)
  - Oregon Liquor Control Commission, undated (Box-folder 26/34)
  - Oregon Portland Cement Co., 1962 (Box-folder 26/35)
  - Oregon Posture Queen, 1964 (Box-folder 26/36)
  - Oregon sea lions caves, 1961 (Box-folder 26/37)
  - Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1964 (Box-folder 26/38)
  - Oregon--Southern, 1961 (Box-folder 26/39)
  - Oregon Stamp Society, 1960 (Box-folder 26/40)
  - Oregon State Capitol, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 26/41)
  - Oregon State Employment Service, 1961 (Box-folder 26/42)
  - Oregon State Fair, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 26/43)
  - Oregon State Fair (schedules, exhibits, other paper records), undated (Box-folder 26/44)
  - Oregon State Hospital (group therapy session), 1962 (Box-folder 26/45)
  - Oregon State Prison, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 26/46)
  - Oregon State University, 1961-1962; 964 (Box-folder 26/47)
  - Oregon State University--Water Laboratory, 1964 (Box-folder 26/48)
  - Oregon State Welfare, 1961 (Box-folder 27/1)
  - Oregonian Building (with striking workers), 1960 (Box-folder 27/2)
  - Organ, 1964 (Box-folder 27/3)
  - Our Lady of Providence Nursery, 1960 (Box-folder 27/4)
  - Pacific Carbide and Alloys Co., 1960 (Box-folder 27/5)
  - Pacific City, Or., undated (Box-folder 27/6)
  - Pacific Inland Navigation Co., undated (Box-folder 27/7)
  - Pacific Lutheran University, 1962 (Box-folder 27/8)
  - Pacific Northwest Bell, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 27/9)
  - Pacific Supply Cooperative, 1964 (Box-folder 27/10)
  - Pacific University, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 27/11)
  - Paisley, Or., 1961 (Box-folder 27/12)
  - Palisades--Canyon, 1961 (Box-folder 27/13)
  - Palm Springs, Calif., 1961 (Box-folder 27/14)
  - Panama Canal Zone, 1964 (Box-folder 27/15)
  - Pancakes, 1961 (Box-folder 27/16)
  - Paper, 1962 (Box-folder 27/17)
  - Paper Dolls, 1964 (Box-folder 27/18)
  - Parachutes, 1963 (Box-folder 27/19)
  - Parachutist, 1962 (Box-folder 128/11)
  - Parades, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 27/20)
  - Parade--Family tale, 1960-1961; 1963 (Box-folder 27/21)
  - Parade--Naval Reserve, 1964 (Box-folder 128/12)
  - Parade--Park Bureau, 1964 (Box-folder 27/22)
  - Parade--Transportation Parade, 1964 (Box-folder 27/23)
  - Parent Teacher Association, 1964 (Box-folder 27/24)
  - Paris, France, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 27/25)
  - Park Bureau (see also Parks, Portland Bureau), 1960; 1962-1963 (Box-folder 27/26)
  - Park Blocks, 1964 (Box-folder 128/13)
  - Park Blocks, 1964 (Box-folder Oversize B1/12)
  - Parks
    - Azalea State Park, 1960 (Box-folder 27/27)
    - Blue Lake, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 27/28)
    - Cape Sebastian, 1963 (Box-folder 27/29)
    - Champoeg, 1964 (Box-folder 27/30)
    - Chapman, 1962 (Box-folder 27/31)
      First high tension power line, 1889--dedication, Lange Syne Society)
    - Clackamas County, 1963 (Box-folder 27/32)
    - Collier State Park, 1962 (Box-folder 27/33)
    - Cove Palisades State Park, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 27/34)
    - Crater Lake, 1961 (Box-folder 27/35)
    - Duniway, 1960 (Box-folder 27/36)
    - Ecola, 1961 (Box-folder 27/37)
    - Forest, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 27/38)
    - Fort Stevens, undated (Box-folder 27/39)
    - Golden Gate, 1962 (Box-folder 27/40)
    - Holladay, 1964 (Box-folder 27/41)
    - Honeyman State (Cleawox Lake), 1961 (Box-folder 27/42)
    - Laurelhurst, 1962 (Box-folder 27/43)
    - Lownsdale, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 27/44)
    - Metzler, 1964 (Box-folder 27/45)
    - Harry E. Morgan (Spirit Lake, Wash.), 1961 (Box-folder 28/1)
    - Mount Tabor, 1962 (Box-folder 28/2)
    - Nesika, 1961 (Box-folder 28/3)
    - North Clackamas, Central, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 28/4)
    - Oaks, 1963 (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Cape Lookout, 1964; undated (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Oxbow, 1964 (Box-folder 28/7)
    - Painted Hill State Park, 1961 (Box-folder 28/8)
    - Portland, 1963 (Box-folder 128/14)
    - Portland Bureau (see also Park Bureau), 1961-1964 (Box-folder 28/9)
    - Powers (damage), undated (Box-folder 128/15)
    - Rocky Mountains, 1961 (Box-folder 28/10)
    - Shore Acres State, 1962 (Box-folder 28/11)
    - Smith Rocks, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 28/12)
  - Parking meters, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 28/13)
  - Pets--Exotic, 1964 (Box-folder 28/14)
  - Picnic--Lloyd Center executives, undated (Box-folder 28/15)
  - Portland Center Redevelopment dedication ceremony, 1964 (Box-folder 28/16)
  - Pumpkins, 1964 (Box-folder 28/17)
  - Railroad accidents, 1964 (Box-folder 28/18)
  - Railroad--Map of proposed merger, 1964 (Box-folder 28/19)
  - Red Higgins Ranch--Wallowa, 1961 (Box-folder 28/20)
  - Rescue--L.A. Fire Department, 1964 (Box-folder 28/21)
  - Rescue--Wild seas, 1964 (Box-folder 28/22)
  - Road repair, undated (Box-folder 28/23)
  - Rose Festival
    - Rose Festival (general), 1964 (Box-folder 28/24)
    - Rose Festival (general), 1963 (Box-folder 128/16)
    - All-City Orchestra, 1964 (Box-folder 128/17)
    - Grand Floral Parade, 1961 (Box-folder 28/25-26)
    - Grand Floral Parade, 1963 (Box-folder 28/27-28)
    - Grand Floral Parade, 1963 (Box-folder 128/18)
    - Grand Floral Parade, 1964 (Box-folder 29/1-2)
    - Holladay Park, 1963 (Box-folder 29/3)
    - Holladay Park, 1963 (Box-folder 128/19)
    - Holladay Park, 1964 (Box-folder 29/4)
    - Hospitals, 1964 (Box-folder 29/5)
    - Junior, 1963 (Box-folder 29/6)
    - Junior--Court, 1964 (Box-folder 29/7)
    - Junior Parade, 1963 (Box-folder 29/8-9)
    - Junior Parade, 1964 (Box-folder 29/10-11)
    - Junior Parade--Animals, 1964 (Box-folder 29/12)
    - Juniors, 1964 (Box-folder 128/20)
    - Marine Day, 1964 (Box-folder 29/13)
    - Merrykhana Parade, 1964 (Box-folder 29/14)
    - Music Festival, 1964 (Box-folder 29/15)
    - Queen selection, 1963 (Box-folder 30/1-3)
    - Queen selection, 1964 (Box-folder 30/4-7)
    - Queen selection, 1964 (Box-folder 128/21)
    - Rose Show, 1964 (Box-folder 30/8)
    - Ships, 1963 (Box-folder 30/9)
    - Ships, 1964 (Box-folder 30/10)
    - Ships (newspaper), 1964 (Box-folder 128/22)
    - Ski meet, 1964 (Box-folder 30/11)
    - Sports events, 1963 (Box-folder 30/12)
    - Sports events, 1964 (Box-folder 30/13)
  - Roseburg, Or.--United State National Bank branch, 1961 (Box-folder 31/1)
  - Roslyn, Wash., 1962 (Box-folder 31/2)
  - Royal Mounted Police, 1962 (Box-folder 31/3)
  - Royal Rosarians, 1961 (Box-folder 31/4)
  - Rugs--Hooked, 1962 (Box-folder 31/5)
  - Rummage sale, 1962 (Box-folder 31/6)
  - Russians in Portland, 1964 (Box-folder 31/7)
  - Rowan and Martin, 1964 (Box-folder 31/8)
  - Ryderwood, Wash., 1961 (Box-folder 31/9)
  - Safeway Stores, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 31/10)
  - Salem, Or., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 31/11)
  - Salishan, Or., 1964 (Box-folder 31/12)
  - Salvation Army, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 31/13)
  - San Francisco, Calif., 1962-1963 (Box-folder 31/14)
  - San Juan Islands, 1963 (Box-folder 31/15)
  - San Marino, 1962 (Box-folder 31/16)
  - San Quentin Prison, 1962 (Box-folder 31/17)
  - Sanctuary of Our Sorrowful Mother, 1960 (Box-folder 31/18)
  - Sand dunes, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 31/19)
  - Sandy, Or.--Fire, 1962 (Box-folder 31/20)
  - Sandy River, 1963 (Box-folder 31/21)
  - Sandy River--Oxbow Project, 1962 (Box-folder 31/22)
  - Santa Claus, 1963 (Box-folder 31/23)
  - Santiam Pass, 1964 (Box-folder 31/24)
  - Sassafras tea, 1962 (Box-folder 31/25)
  - St. Helens, Or., 1960-1961 (Box-folder 31/26)
  - St. Paul, Or.-Rodeo, 1962 (Box-folder 31/27)
  - St. Vincent de Paul, 1961 (Box-folder 31/28)
  - Satellites, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 31/29)
  - Sauvie Island, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 31/30)
  - Saw, 1963 (Box-folder 31/31)
  - Sawyer's, 1961 (Box-folder 31/32)
  - Schnitzer Industries, 1962 (Box-folder 31/33)
  - Schools
    - Beaverton, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 31/34)
    - Chemawa Indian, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 31/35)
    - Chinese, 1961 (Box-folder 31/36)
    - Christie, 1961 (Box-folder 31/37)
    - Collins View, 1962 (Box-folder 31/38)
    - Columbia, 1962 (Box-folder 31/39)
    - Emily School for the Handicapped (includes School for Retarded), 1962-1963 (Box-folder 31/40)
    - Happy Hollow, 1962 (Box-folder 31/41)
    - Hayhurst, 1960 (Box-folder 31/42)
    - Hillsboro High School, 1961 (Box-folder 31/43)
    - Holy Trinity, 1962 (Box-folder 31/44)
    - Jenning Lodge, 1961 (Box-folder 31/45)
    - Jesuit, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 31/46)
    - Lynch Plaza, 1961 (Box-folder 31/47)
    - Martin Luther, 1963 (Box-folder 31/48)
    - Marycrest, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 31/49)
    - Mayville, Wis.--High School, 1964 (Box-folder 31/50)
    - Medford, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 31/51)
    - Pacific University, 1964 (Box-folder 31/52)
    - Parkrose, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 31/53)
    - Portland, 1960-1961; 1964 (Box-folder 32/1)
    - Portland, 1961 (Box-folder 128/23)
    - Portland--Ascension, 1962 (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Portland--Ainsworth, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 32/3)
    - Portland--Astor, 1961 (Box-folder 32/4)
    - Portland--Atkinson, 1962 (Box-folder 32/5)
    - Portland--Benson High, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 32/6)
    - Portland--Bridlemile, 1963 (Box-folder 32/7)
    - Portland--Brooklyn, 1964 (Box-folder 32/8)
    - Portland--Buckman, 1961 (Box-folder 32/9)
    - Portland--Catlin Gable, 1960-1961; 1963 (Box-folder 32/10)
    - Portland--Central Catholic, 1964 (Box-folder 32/11)
    - Portland--Chief Joseph, 1962 (Box-folder 32/12)
    - Portland--Portland Christian, 1962 (Box-folder 32/13)
    - Portland--Christie, 1963 (Box-folder 32/14)
    - Portland--Cleveland, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 32/15)
    - Portland--Columbia High, 1963 (Box-folder 32/16)
    - Portland--Couch, 1962 (Box-folder 32/17)
    - Portland--Creston, 1961 (Box-folder 32/18)
    - Portland--David Douglas, 1963 (Box-folder 32/19)
    - Portland--Fernwood, 1961 (Box-folder 32/20)
    - Portland--Franklin, 1962 (Box-folder 32/21)
    - Portland--George, 1962 (Box-folder 32/22)
    - Portland--Gregory Heights, 1963 (Box-folder 32/23)
    - Portland--Girls Polytechnic, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 32/24)
    - Portland--Glenhaven, 1963 (Box-folder 32/25)
    - Portland--Grant, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 32/26)
    - Portland--Holladay, 1960 (Box-folder 32/27)
    - Portland--Holy Child, 1963 (Box-folder 32/28)
    - Portland--Holy Redeemer, 1963 (Box-folder 32/29)
    - Portland--Hosford, 1961 (Box-folder 32/30)
    - Portland--James John, 1961 (Box-folder 32/31)
    - Portland--Jonathan Edwards, 1961 (Box-folder 32/32)
    - Portland--Jefferson, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 32/33)
    - Portland--Kellogg, 1962 (Box-folder 32/34)
    - Portland--Kenton, 1960 (Box-folder 32/35)
    - Portland--Laurelhurst, 1961 (Box-folder 32/36)
    - Portland--Lincoln, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 32/37)
    - Portland--Madison, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 32/38)
    - Portland--Marquam, 1961 (Box-folder 32/39)
    - Portland--Marshall, John, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 32/40)
    - Portland--Montessori, 1962 (Box-folder 32/41)
    - Portland--Mt. Tabor, 1962 (Box-folder 32/42)
    - Portland--North Catholic, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 32/43)
    - Portland--Our Lady of Sorrows, 1961 (Box-folder 32/44)
    - Portland--Portland State College and University, 1964 (Box-folder 32/45)
    - Portland--Roosevelt, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 32/46)
    - Portland--Shattuck, 1962 (Box-folder 32/47)
    - Portland--Sitton, 1962 (Box-folder 32/48)
    - Portland--St. Francis, 1963 (Box-folder 33/1)
    - Portland--St. Helens Hall, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 33/2)
    - Portland--St. Mary's Academy, 1963 (Box-folder 33/3)
    - Portland--St. Mary's Cathedral, 1963 (Box-folder 33/4)
    - Portland--St. Theresa, 1960 (Box-folder 33/5)
    - Portland--Summer session, 1963 (Box-folder 33/6)
    - Portland--Tucker-Maxon, 1961 (Box-folder 33/7)
    - Portland--Vernon, 1961 (Box-folder 33/8)
    - Portland--Washington, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 33/9)
    - Portland--Western Business University, 1963 (Box-folder 33/10)
    - Portland--Whitaker, 1963 (Box-folder 33/11)
    - Portland--Wilson, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 33/12)
    - Prescott--F89 Scorpion Crash, 1962 (Box-folder 33/13)
    - Ridgewood, 1963 (Box-folder 33/14)
    - Seattle (Phantom Lake School, Twin Lakes Area), 1961 (Box-folder 33/15)
    - St. Mary's Home for Boys, 1963 (Box-folder 33/16)
    - South Rockwood, 1961 (Box-folder 128/24)
    - Summer school, St. Helens, Or. (1924 letter only; negative removed) (Box-folder 33/17)
    - Sunset High, 1964 (Box-folder 33/18)
    - Texas Kilgore Rangerettes, 1964 (Box-folder 33/19)
    - Unidentified, circa 1900 (Box-folder 33/20)
    - Washington County for Retarded Children (Aloha), 1962 (Box-folder 33/21)
    - Washington (Vancouver) State School for the Deaf, 1964 (Box-folder 33/22)
  - Science fair, 1961 (Box-folder 33/23)
  - Scientific laboratory, 1961 (Box-folder 33/24)
  - Scoopmobile, 1962 (Box-folder 33/25)
  - Scotland, 1962 (Box-folder 33/26)
  - Scuba, 1962 (Box-folder 33/27)
  - Sculptures, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 33/28)
  - Sea Lion Caves (Elevator, Florence, Or.), 1961 (Box-folder 33/29)
  - Seabees, 1962 (Box-folder 33/30)
  - Seals, Christmas, 1964 (Box-folder 33/31)
  - Seamen, 1963 (Box-folder 33/32)
  - Sears, Roebuck and Co.--High Fashion Board, 1964 (Box-folder 33/33)
  - Seaside, Or., 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 33/34)
  - Seaside, Or.--Riot, 1964 (Box-folder 33/35-36)
  - Seattle, Wash., 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 33/37)
  - Seattle, Wash.--Century 21, 1963 (Box-folder 34/1-3)
  - Seattle, Wash.--City Jail Farm, 1961 (Box-folder 34/4)
  - Seattle, Wash.--Seafare, 1962 (Box-folder 34/5)
  - Seattle University, 1962 (Box-folder 34/6)
  - Service station, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 34/7)
  - Settlement, Chamizal (Bridge in El Paso where presidents of U.S. and Mexico will meet), 1964 (Box-folder 34/8)
  - Sewers--Portland, 1961 (Box-folder 34/9)
  - Sewers--Oak Lodge, 1961 (Box-folder 34/10)
  - Sewers--West Slope, 1961 (Box-folder 34/11)
  - Sewing machines, 1962 (Box-folder 34/12)
  - Shake-A-Ply Co., 1963 (Box-folder 34/13)
  - Shedd, Or., 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 34/14)
  - Shells, 1962 (Box-folder 34/15)
  - Sheraton Motor Inn, 1963 (Box-folder 34/16)
  - Sheriff--Clackamas County, 1963 (Box-folder 34/17)
  - Ships
    - General, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 34/18)
    - A, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 34/19)
    - Acoma, 1962 (Box-folder 128/25)
    - B, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 34/20)
    - C, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 34/21)
    - Cuba, 1962 (Box-folder 34/22)
    - Cuba, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 34/23)
    - F, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 34/24)
    - E, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 34/25)
    - G, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 34/26)
    - H, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 34/27)
    - Helena, U.S.S., 1961 (Box-folder 128/26)
    - I, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 34/28)
    - Indonesian, 1961 (Box-folder 34/29)
    - J, 1963 (Box-folder 34/30)
    - Japan, 1960 (Box-folder 34/31)
    - K, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 35/1)
    - L, 1960-1961; 1964 (Box-folder 35/2)
    - M, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 35/3)
    - Model--Kennedy, John F., 1961 (Box-folder 35/4)
    - N, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 35/5)
    - O, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 35/6)
    - P, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 35/7)
    - Q, 1962 (Box-folder 35/8)
    - R, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 35/9)
    - Russian, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 35/10)
    - S, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 35/11)
    - Submarines--Arch fish, 1964 (Box-folder 35/12)
    - Submarines--Blackfin, 1962 (Box-folder 35/13)
    - Submarines--D, 1964 (Box-folder 35/14)
    - Submarines--England, 1961 (Box-folder 35/15)
    - Submarines--T, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 35/16)
    - T (Ships, cont.), 1960; 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 35/17)
    - U, 1969; 1962 (Box-folder 35/18)
    - V, 1961 (Box-folder 35/19)
    - W, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 35/20)
    - Y, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 35/21)
    - Disaster, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 35/22)
  - Shoes, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 35/23)
  - Shopping center, 1962 (Box-folder 35/24)
  - Shoppers, undated (Box-folder 35/25)
  - Shorts, 1961 (Box-folder 35/26)
  - Short Sand Beach, 1961 (Box-folder 35/27)
  - Shots, 1962 (Box-folder 35/28)
  - Shriners, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 35/29)
  - Sierra Leone, 1961 (Box-folder 35/30)
  - Signs, 1963 (Box-folder 35/31)
  - Siltcoos Lake, 1961 (Box-folder 35/32)
  - Sliver, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 35/33)
  - Sliver City, 1961 (Box-folder 35/34)
  - Sliver Lake, 1961 (Box-folder 35/35)
  - Sisters of St. Mary's of the Valley, 1964 (Box-folder 35/36)
  - SKF Industries, 1961 (Box-folder 35/37)
  - Skamania Landing development, 1964 (Box-folder 35/38)
  - Skateboarding, 1963 (Box-folder 35/39)
  - Skates, 1961 (Box-folder 35/40)